sonniss.com 2017-07-31

# Privacy Policy | Sonniss.com

This Privacy Policy (referred to herein as ‘Policy’) has been created to inform you about how we deal with privacy concerns here at Sonniss. Your privacy is very important to us and for that reason, you must agree to the terms of this Policy before using our website.

**This Policy governs all of the information that we collect about you and how we use the collected information. By accepting this Policy and the terms & conditions of the marketplace, you consent to our use of your personal information in the manner outlined within this Policy. You acknowledge this Policy by using the Site.**

## Information Collection

Our ONLY purpose in collecting your personal information is to provide you with a better trading experience and to encourage ongoing commerce between buyers and sellers using this Site. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for this purpose and to achieve this goal. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information and can access many aspects of the Site without providing us any personal information.

**When you visit this website, we can record certain information in relation to your visit such as:**

  * Your IP or proxy server IP;
  * Basic domain information;
  * Your Internet service provider is sometimes captured
  * The date and time of your visit to the website;
  * The length of your session;
  * The pages which you have accessed;
  * The number of times you access our site within any month;
  * The size of file you look at;
  * The website which referred you to our website; and
  * The operating system which your computer uses.

Various pages on this Site also invite you to provide us with your name and contact details, for example, to be added to our mailing list for our newsletter or to enter competitions.

**The Site uses session cookies, which are used only during a browsing session, and expire when you quit your browser. Upon closing your browser, the session cookie set by this Site is destroyed and no personal information is maintained which might identify you should you visit our Site at a later date.**

If you choose to buy or sell sound effect libraries using this Site, we collect information about your buying and selling behavior. This information is only used for statistical and website development purposes.

We also collect information from people who use this site, to send news, information about our activities and general promotional material which we believe may be useful to you or us;  
to monitor who is accessing the Site and to profile the type of people accessing the Site.

If you use a payment facilitator on the Site, we may collect additional necessary information, including but not limited to billing address, Country of origin and Phone number. No credit card details are ever stored.

## USE OF INFORMATION AND DISCLOSURE

We only use the collected information for the following purposes:

  * Forwarding important information relating to Sonniss and other requested information;
  * Contacting you in response to your feedback or query;
  * Monitoring Site performance;
  * Improving our Site and services to you;
  * Internal administration; and
  * Other purposes that are in accordance with your instructions.

**We do not store credit card details nor do we share financial details with any 3rd parties.** Sonniss will not give, sell, trade or otherwise disclose any personal information about you to a third party unless we are required to do so under European law.

## COOKIES AND ADVERTISING

Occasionally, we may use third party advertising companies to serve ads based on prior visits to the Site. These advertising companies use cookies to anonymously collect data. No personally identifiable information is collected by these cookies. The anonymous data they collect is kept separate from the personal information in your account. You can opt out of third party advertising cookies at any time.

We use third party analytics services that use cookies to record general site usage information – like page visits and the way users move between pages on the Site. This general site analytics information is not matched to your user account. Other cookies are used to enhance your use of the Site, such as remembering that you are logged in. You are able to minimise or block cookies using the privacy settings in your internet browser, but this may restrict your use of the Site. For general information on cookies, see http://www.allaboutcookies.org/

## DISCLAIMER

This Site contains some links to other sites. Sonniss is not responsible for the privacy practices of linked sites, or the content. Underlined words and phrases are click-through links or hyperlinks to pages and websites.

## SECURITY

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss or misuse of, or alteration or unauthorised access to, information under our control. However, if you send information from this Site, it will not be encrypted unless we expressly tell you it is.

## AMENDMENTS TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this Policy. Such changes will be effective when a notice of the change is made available on the Site. We will provide you with thirty (30) days notice to allow you the opportunity to notify Sonniss if you do not agree to such changes.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF INFORMATION

Sonniss uses Amazon S3 / Cloudfront for storage & serving, thus meaning the information collected from you will be stored in these countries. By voluntarily providing information to us when using the Site, you are consenting to the collection and use of your personal information by us.

## FURTHER INFORMATION

For further information about Sonnis’s privacy policy, please contact support.
